[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the smallest species of dolphin?", "correct_answer": "Maui Dolphin/Hectors Dolphin", "incorrect_answers": ["The Spinner Dolphin", "The Pacific White-Sided Dolphin", "The Bottlenose Dolphin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What adjectives best describe Robert De Niros character Jake LaMotta in the 1980 movie Raging Bull?", "correct_answer": "Aggressive", "incorrect_answers": ["Kind-hearted and sympathetic", "Quiet and diffident", "Wise and prudent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest sea in the world?", "correct_answer": "South China Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Caribbean Sea", "Mediterranean Sea", "Bering Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first guest host on NBCs Saturday Night Live?", "correct_answer": "George Carlin", "incorrect_answers": ["John  Goodman", "Howard Cosell", "Steve Martin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For over 1000 years most people believed that the sun circled the Earth. The  scientific basis for this  came from the book The Almagest written by this thinker.", "correct_answer": "Ptolemy", "incorrect_answers": ["Aristarchus", "Hipparchus", "Aristotle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the director of the 1975 movie One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest?", "correct_answer": "Milos Forman", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin Scorsese", "Stanley Kubrick", "Quentin Tarantino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Parthenogenesis (from Greek - virgin creation), an asexual way of reproduction without the need of fertilization, occurs naturally in these animals.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Birds", "Reptiles", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie The Shawshank Redemption hit the movie theatres?", "correct_answer": "1994", "incorrect_answers": ["1992", "1990", "1996"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the high school that Carrie White attended in the 70s movie Carrie?", "correct_answer": "Bates High School", "incorrect_answers": ["Berkowitz High School", "Manson High School", "Wilkes High School"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2002, which battery manufacturer announced the development of a battery, which would fully recharge in 15 minutes or less?", "correct_answer": "Rayovac", "incorrect_answers": ["Duracell", "Energizer", "Sony"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the opening credits of The Breakfast Club, the guidance counselors desk is shown with his nameplate. What is the name and what is the significance?", "correct_answer": "R. Hashimoto, executive producer of the film", "incorrect_answers": ["P. Gleason, actor in the film", "J. Hughes, director of the film", "R. Reagan, president of the US"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Green Mile, Tom Hanks plays Paul Edgecomb, but he was not the first choice for the role. Who was originally considered for the role?", "correct_answer": "John Travolta", "incorrect_answers": ["George Clooney", "Bruce Willis", "Tim Robbins"]}]